<dashboard  version="1.1" stylesheet="tutorial.css">
  <label>FAQ</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <p>
          <b>Question: I'm getting confused with these new terms like toolbox, tooltip, dataZoom, series.. Where is a good starting point?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: Check out the <a href="https://echarts.apache.org/en/cheat-sheet.html" target="_blank">ECharts Cheat Sheet</a>. It's a great starting point to get familiar with the terms.
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: The visualization failes loading and prints out "Error rendering Visualization Toolbox visualization"</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: We suggest the following steps to solve this issue: First copy your options code to <a href="https://echarts.apache.org/examples/en/editor.html" target="_blank">echarts example page (IDE)</a> to check if there is an sytax error in your options.
          Second check the data mapping: seriesDataIndexBinding, xAxisDataIndexBinding. 
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: Does visualization toolbox support Dashboard Studio?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: As Dashboard Studio does no support custom visualizations, the visualization toolki is not supported in Dashboard Studio.
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: Does visualization toolbox support Splunk Mobile?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: As Splunk Mobile app does no support custom visualizations, the visualization toolbox is not supported using Splunk Mobile.
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: I want to use visualization toolbox within my own business critial app. Do you have support offerings?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: Generally speaking the app is free to use. You can connect to us using the <a href="https://github.com/hman-78/visualization_toolbox/issues" target="_blank">github issue tracker</a>. We will try to answer your questions as soon as possible.
          If this is not enough for you, we offer paid support, consulting and training for the app. Please contact us via email: XXX . 
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: Is visualization toolbox running on Splunk Cloud?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: Yes, we tested it on Splunk Cloud. If you find any issues, please let us know via <a href="https://github.com/hman-78/visualization_toolbox/issues" target="_blank">github issue tracker</a>.
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>
          <b>Question: I need feature XYZ in my chart. How do I configure it?</b>
        </p>
        <p>
          Answer: We suggest using <a href="https://echarts.apache.org/examples/en/editor.html" target="_blank">ECharts example page (IDE)</a> and <a href="https://echarts.apache.org/en/option.html#title">Chart Option Documentation</a> to create your chart first. 
          Then copy the option code into the visualization toolbox.
        </p>

    </html>
</panel>
</row>
</dashboard>